[{"answer": "Well, I'm going to quote the great Newt Gingrich in saying that the man was lying and this is from a previous debate that Newt Gingrich was in with Mitt Romney.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "The opening question is, what the hell was wrong with Barack Obama last night?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "And that's what I would ask, I would love to honestly hear Newt Gingrich's response to this, because as he said in his previous debates, when he had to -- he backed down a bit, you just cannot debate somebody who's dishonest.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Jennifer Granholm, if Mitt Romney was telling all these lies, why on earth was Barack Obama not correcting them during the debate in front of over 60 million Americans?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "That certainly what the Congressional Budget Office says.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Was that a fact?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Wait a second.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "So in other words, it's not a fact, is it?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "First of all, as Governor Romney pointed out last night, the Mayo Clinic is a private institution run by people privately who do things efficiently, which is very different than the federal government, which has rampant waste.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Where are you going to find $716 billion and it's not going to be because of Big Bird?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Very good question.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Can he name two, at least two of the deductions that will be cut to be able to pay for the $5 trillion tax cut that Romney is offering?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, there are at least two components to how he ends up paying for the tax cut.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Can you explain to us any of the detail?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "No, he said -- no, absolutely not.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Yes or no?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "I don't know the number exactly but I do know that there's a net gain.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "-- since he took over is 125,000 jobs?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Well, we know the jobs report is not going to be good, even if it's better than it has been.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "How important is the jobs report going to be tomorrow to Barack Obama, do you think?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Come on.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "-- is you want four more years like this?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "That's total baloney.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Newt Gingrich, should Big Bird be killed or not?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "So you would save Big Bird?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Big Bird lives.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Jennifer, yes or no, Big Bird, live or die?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Is that what you would like to see?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I am doing great, Piers.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "What did you think?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "I've been to Denver many times.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "You ever suffer altitude problems?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Well, as a matter of fact, I voted to kill Big Bird in the past.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Finally, would you kill Big Bird?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "That was beautifully badly phrased.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Can we go back on that one?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "I don't know what debate Maria was watching, but President Barack Obama was anything but deft.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Crystal, what do you want to say?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "I think that is a very good question, Piers, because you would think that in talking about the preparation, you would take a look at all of the debates and actually, the one with Newt Gingrich is the one that I think they needed to take a look at, because that's where he eviscerated the Speaker.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Has he never seen Mitt Romney debate?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "I tend to agree with you, Piers, because Senator Biden is somebody who is a fire brand for sure.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "Definitely.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Who is going to win?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Look, I'm going to put myself out there.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Crystal, you really think Paul Ryan is going to eviscerate Joe Biden?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "I don't have an answer for you yet because there are a lot of things you have to consider before you make that final decision.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Yes or no, are you going to run for the presidency again?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "The issue of great significance that everybody tells me I should just change my mind on and do the politically expedient thing, which is to say that my health care plan was a terrible mistake, I'm not willing to do.", "docId": "121004pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "Am I right in thinking you know the answer, you just don't want to give it to me yet?", "qSentId": 648}]